## Caitlin Baker

E-mail: caitbaker@gmail.com Contact

Phone:  $+353\ 834777864$ 

Address: Dublin, Ireland

GitHub: github.com/caitbaker

LANGUAGE SKILLS Fluent in English, Portuguese and Spanish.

Professional Objectives

Information

My main skillset lies within research, planning, marketing and customer service. I thrive to improve on these with each new career choice.

My motto in life is that there is always a solution to any problem, "this can't be done" does not exist

for me.

I am a fast problem solver and have an ability to learn new skills in a short period of time as proven by having successfully moved to multiple countries to live, work and study. I am relentlessly resourceful and I am currently learning how to code, as I see technology being at the centre of interesting new developments within my chosen areas of interest.

I am a very communicative person and like teamwork but also work well alone, as you can see in my experience below.

EDUCATION

Dalarna University, Borlange, Sweden

Master of Arts (MA), Tourism Destination Development

2013 - 2014

Escola Superior de Tecnologia e Gestao, IPVC, Viana do Castelo, Portugal

2004 - 2008BA in Tourism

Professional EXPERIENCE

Camelot Group - National Lottery, Dublin, Ireland

Customer Service Representative

November 2014 – December 2014

Answering queries pertaining to the National Lottery.

Trouble shooting technical queries.

FanFootage, Dublin, Ireland

Event Coordinator Intern

September 2014 – Present

Organising sales pipeline by centralising and standardising artist reach-outs.

Produce shows within FanFootage as they happen. This involves communicating with various stakeholders.

Approving videos for use in various events.

Reaching out to various artists to understand their needs/restrictions at events.

Nexeo Solutions Central Office Europe, Barcelona, Spain

Customer Service Representative

June 2012 - June 2013

Back office management and support for Portuguese sales team.

Inputting orders into SAP.

Management of customers' e-mails, faxes and phone calls.

Hotusa Hotels S.A., Barcelona, Spain

Hotel Reservations Agent

December 2011 – February 2012

Reserving accommodation for clients and agencies via telephone and e-mail.

Answering inquiries pertaining to hotel services, B2B and B2C.

## Luxottica Iberia S.A., Barcelona, Spain

Call Centre Agent

July 2011 - November 2011

Customer service B2B through phone, e-mail and fax.

Inputting orders and resolving problems.

## Groundforce, Barcelona, Spain

Check-in Agent

January 2011 – May 2011

Passenger and baggage check-in.

Passenger boarding.

Customer service.

## Ryanair LTD, Stansted Airport, United Kingdom

Cabin Crew

September 2009 - March 2010

Passenger service.

Operational and security processes.

Problem solving.

On board sales.

Computer

Microsoft Office, LaTex, SAP, Oracle and Salesforce.com.

Skills

Hobbies Reading, travelling, hiking, spending time with friends, listening to music and dancing.

References A

Available on request.